#### Contact

laurenesquivel07@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/laurenesquivel-21466b139 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Banking Financial Services Retail Sales

Honors-Awards

President's Honor Roll 2015-2017

# Lauren Esquivel

Nursing Student at West Coast University

Huntington Beach, California

#### Summary

Experienced Operations with a demonstrated history of working in the banking industry. Skilled in Academic Writing, Financial Services, Political Communication, Customer Service, and Microsoft Word. Strong operations professional with a Bachelor of Arts - BA focused in Political Science and Government from California State University, Fullerton.

### Experience

West Coast University
Nursing Student
January 2020 - Present (7 months)

Equinox Membership Advisor October 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months) Orange County, California Area

Freelance Self-Employed Au Pair January 2018 - April 2018 (4 months) Mainz Area, Germany

Union Bank
Operations
August 2015 - December 2017 (2 years 5 months)
Orange County, California Area

Wells Fargo Teller June 2014 - June 2015 (1 year 1 month) Costa Mesa, California

## Education

West Coast University

Bachelor of Science - BS · (2020 - 2022)

California State University, Fullerton

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Political Science and Government · (2015 - 2017)

**Orange Coast College** 

Associate of Arts (AA), Broadcast Journalism · (2012 - 2015)